Guide to the Yale College, Records of the Yale Bands
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale College, Records of the Yale Bands
1901-2013
RU 1140
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
20
This collection contains the records of the Yale Bands, which consists of the Yale Concert Band, the Yale Jazz Ensemble, and the Yale Precision Marching Band.
General
Forms part of the Record Group 9-E (YRG 9-E), Records documenting Yale College offices, programs, and projects.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collection is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Biographical / Historical
The Yale Band's history begins in 1917, when Lt. Joseph Ellis first assembled a group of instrumentalists to do service for Yale College. Various groups of wind, brass, and percussion players presented concerts at Yale throughout the first half of the 20th century. The Yale Concert Band was formed in 1946 with the appointment of Keith L. Wilson, while the Yale Jazz Ensemble traces its official roots to the 1970s.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes photographs, performance memorabilia, correspondence, videos and newsclippings from performances, tours, and other events by the Yale Concert Band, the Yale Jazz Ensemble and the Yale Precision Marching Band.
Band music; Bands (Music) -- Pictorial works; Jazz; Music in universities and colleges
- Records, 1901-2013; Accession 2015-A-063
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2049.
  - Documents
    - Administrative records, 1940-2009 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
    - Articles and news clippings
      - Circa 1910-1912 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Circa 1920-1927 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Charles E. Smith, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - 1930-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1-13)
      - 1976-1987 (Box 3, Folder 1-14)
      - 1988-2013 (Box 4, Folder 1-17)
      - Undated (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
    - Audio-visual container labels and inserts, 2001-2013 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Band humor (samples), 1983-1989, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Calendars, 2007-2013 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Commencement, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Concert band schedule, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence
      - 1941-1983 (Box 5, Folder 4-12)
      - 1984-2010 (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
      - Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Christmas cards, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Christmas cards of the Yale Precision Marching Band, 1978-1988, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Duffy, Thomas - awards and recognition, 2002-2009 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ephemera, 1924-circa 2013 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Scope and Contents
      Material includes menus, tickets, sticker, and copy of luggage tag.
    - European tours
      - News clippings, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - 1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - 1965 (Box 7, Folder 5-8)
      - 1968 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
      - Souvenir cards from PanAm, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - "Let Freedom Ring - A Concert Tour of Eastern Europe, May 28-June 12, 1991" (viewbook), 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Football song contest, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
    - Fok, Tony - concert reviews of February 26 Carnegie Hall performance, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Glenn Miller Band re-enactment
      - Advertisements and reviews, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence and research material, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence and reviews, 1992-2004 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Fundraising: donations solicited with Glenn Miller brochure, including thank-you letters, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
        Restricted until January 1, 2030.
      - News clippings, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - "Yale Remembers World War II"
        - Correspondence and documents, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
        - Testimony file, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - History of the band - research material, Circa 1920-1990, undated (Box 12, Folder 1-7)
    - Japan - postcards, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Marching band formation diagrams, 1977, undated (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
    - Marching band mailers, 1986-1996 (Box 12, Folder 11-13)
    - National Wind Ensemble Conference, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Newsletters, 1958-1996 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
    - "Music at Yale: A Quarterly Report"
      - Volume 1, numbers 3-4, 1972 spring/summer (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Volume 4, numbers 1-2, 1974 fall/winter (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Posters
      - General, 1968-2008, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
        Material includes flyers and otjher informational material.
        - Oversize negative, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Concert Band, 2003-2010, undated (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
        - Oversize, 1988-2005, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Jazz Ensemble, 2002-2010, undated (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
    - Press releases, 1973-1986 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Programs
      - 1922-1957 (Box 15, Folder 1-5)
      - 1958-1967 (Box 16, Folder 1-6)
      - 1968-2013 (Box 17, Folder 1-6)
      - Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Publicity, 1959, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Regulations of the Yale University Bands, Circa 1960s (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Rich, Buddy - concert, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Sheet music, 1902-1964 (Box 18, Folder 2-4)
      - Oversize, 1907-1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Photographs
    - Chronological, 1902-2005 (Box 20, Folder 1-9)
    - Subject
      - General
        - Yale Band, photographer Harold Shapiro, 2006
        - Yale Band Parents' Weekend and Veterans Concert, photographer Harold Shapiro, 2006
        - Yale Band, photographer Harold Shapiro, 2007
        - Concert Band, etc., photographer Harold Shapiro, 2008
        - Yale Band, photographer Harold Shapiro, 2008 November
      - Banjo Club alumni, Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Bush, George H. W., inaugural parade, 1989 January 20 (Box 21, Folder 2)
        - Oversize (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Commencement, Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Concert Band
        - Beinecke concerts, 1976, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
        - Formal group portraits
          - 1901-1902 (Box 22, Folder 1)
          - 1946-1947 (Box 22, Folder 2)
          - 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 3)
          - 1949-1950 (Box 22, Folder 4)
          - 1951-1952 (Box 22, Folder 5)
          - 1956-1968 (Box 22, Folder 6-14)
          - 1975 (Box 22, Folder 15)
          - 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 16)
          - 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 17)
          - 2004-2006 (Box 22, Folder 18-19)
          - Concert Band professional photo shoot, photographer Harold Shapiro, 2005 February 15
          - 2008 November (Box 22, Folder 20)
          - 2010 (Box 22, Folder 21)
          - Undated (Box 22, Folder 22-24)
        - Individuals, unidentified, 1969-1970, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
        - Members of band, unidentified, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
        - Performances
          - General
            - 1955-1956 (Box 21, Folder 7)
            - 1979-1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
            - Undated (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
          - Glenn Miller Band re-enactments, 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 11-13)
            General
            See also Glenn Miller Show and Tour album in box 27, folders 1-3.
            - Oversize (Box 32, Folder 2)
          - Gusman Hall, University of Miami, 1975-03 (Box 23, Folder 1)
          - Hopkins School, 1974 October (Box 23, Folder 2)
          - Indifferent Voices, 1975 March 5-7 (Box 23, Folder 3)
          - Outdoor performances, unidentified, Undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
          - Parents' Weekend Concert, James R. Anderson Photography, 2008 October 25
          - Woolsey Hall
            - Cole Porter Pops Concert, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 5)
            - Yale and Coast Guard Concert, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
            - Unidentified, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7-9)
        - Rehearsals
          - 1955-1956 (Box 23, Folder 10)
          - 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 11)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 12)
          - 1980 (Box 23, Folder 13)
          - Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
        - Tours
          - California, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
          - Europe
            - 1959 (Box 24, Folder 2-6)
            - 1962 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
            - 1965 (Box 25, Folder 1-5)
            - 1969 (Box 25, Folder 6)
            - 1972 (Box 25, Folder 7)
            - 1976 (Box 25, Folder 8-10, Box 26, Folder 1-3)
            - Stockholm, 1976 June 8 (Box 26, Folder 4)
            - Glenn Miller Show and Tour album, Circa 1994 (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
              See also Glenn Miller Band re-enactments in box 21, folders 11-13.
            - 2001 (Box 26, Folder 5)
          - Florida, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
          - Japan, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 7)
          - Texas, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 8)
          - Texas and Puerto Rico, 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 1)
          - Bermuda, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Eton group picture, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Glenn Miller Band, Circa 1938-1944 (Box 28, Folder 3-5)
        Material includes reprints of original photographs.
      - Glenn Miller monument, Grove Street Cemetary, Circa 1994 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Individuals
        - Arvantely, Peter T., Undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
        - Baum, Gerald, Undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
        - Borge, Victor, Undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
        - Brion, Keith, Undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
        - Centuori, Dante, Circa 1985 (Box 28, Folder 11)
        - Cook, Eugene, 1976 March 7 (Box 28, Folder 12)
        - Cronkite, Walter, with others, Circa 1993 (Box 28, Folder 13)
        - Duffy, Thomas, Undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
        - Duffy, Thomas, and others, Undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
        - Gibb, Arthur, auditioning trumpet, Circa 1957 (Box 28, Folder 16)
        - Gillespie, Allen, Undated (Box 28, Folder 17)
        - Husa, Karl, Undated (Box 28, Folder 18)
        - Past, Peter, Undated (Box 28, Folder 19)
        - Platt, Richard, band librarian, Circa 1995 (Box 28, Folder 20)
        - Ruff, Willie, Undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
        - Wilson, Richard, 1957-1972, undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
        - Wyner, Susan Davenny, Undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
        - Unidentified individuals, Undated (Box 28, Folder 24-25)
      - Instruments, Undated (Box 28, Folder 26)
      - Precision Marching Band
        - General photographs
          - Roy E. Nanjo, photographer, Circa 1981 (Box 29, Folder 1)
          - Unidentified photographer, Circa 1981 (Box 29, Folder 2)
          - 2008 (Box 32, Folder 4)
          - 2008-2009 (Box 33, Folder 1)
        - Boarding trucks for transport, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Director on field, Undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - Group photographs
          - 1902 (Box 31, Folder 1)
          - 1924-1958 (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
          - 1960-1971, undated (Box 29, Folder 5-7)
          - 1985 (Box 33, Folder 2)
          - 2008 (Box 32, Folder 5)
          - 2008-2009 (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - Hockey, Undated (Box 29, Folder 8-9)
        - On the field
          - Harvard halftime, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 10)
          - Brown game, 1942 (Box 29, Folder 11)
          - 1953-1957 (Box 29, Folder 12)
          - Pete Sauers and others, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 13)
          - 1960-1970 (Box 29, Folder 14)
          - Circa 1973-1979 (Box 29, Folder 15)
          - 1981-1984 (Box 29, Folder 16)
          - 1992 (Box 29, Folder 17)
          - 2008-2009 (Box 33, Folder 4)
          - Guests and alumni members, Undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
          - Undated (Box 29, Folder 19-21)
        - On the sidelines
          - 1976 (Box 29, Folder 22)
          - 2008-2009 (Box 33, Folder 5)
          - Trumpets leading a fight cheer, Undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
          - Undated (Box 29, Folder 24-25)
        - Painting the Yale Bowl benches, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 26)
        - Parades, Undated (Box 29, Folder 27-28)
      - Social events - dinners, receptions, parties, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Travel, Undated (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
      - Visiting musician teaching class, Undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Yale Collegians, Circa 1930 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Slides, negatives, and contact sheets
      - Slides
        - 1994 (Box 34, Folder 1)
        - Undated (Box 34, Folder 2-3)
      - Negatives
        - 1960-1972 (Box 34, Folder 4)
        - Commencement, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 5)
        - Sixth European tour, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
        - Alumni Weekend, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 7)
        - Glenn Miller Show and Tour album, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 8)
        - Undated (Box 34, Folder 9-11)
      - Contact sheet prints
        - 1960-1979 (Box 34, Folder 12)
        - Glenn Miller Show and Tour album, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 13)
        - 2004-2008 (Box 34, Folder 14)
        - Undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Audiovisual material
    - General
      - Duffy project, 2002; 1 (Box 541)
      - Sights and Sounds of Yale Music, 2010
      - Levin Opus 20: A Musical Tribute to Jane & Rick Levin, 2013 February 14
      - Duffy FCP raw, Undated
      - Rich Gabriel, Tom Duffy sound bites, Undated; 1 (Box 542)
      - Importance of 5, 2, Undated (Box 543)
      - Lingenfelter, Undated; 1 (Box 544)
      - Unidentified
        - DAT tape, Undated (Box 545)
        - MiniDV tapes, Undated; 6 (Box 546–551)
      - Phonograph records
        - Cases for records
          - "Songs of Yale: Yale Glee Club, Marshall Bartholomew, conductor and Yale Band, Keith L. Wilson, conductor" case, Circa 1950 (Box 35, Folder 1)
            The case for the three 78rpm records version of this recording inclueds the lyrics for all the songs on the inside back cover.
          - "Songs of Yale: Yale Glee Club, Marshall Bartholomew, conductor and Yale Band, Keith L. Wilson, conductor" LP version case (Box 35, Folder 2)
          - "A Souvenir Album by the Whiffenpoofs, Class of 1942" (Box 35, Folder 3)
            A short history of the Whiffenpoofs and some historical photographs are included on the interior of the case.
        - Vinyl records
          - Songs of Yale: Yale Glee Club, Marshall Bartholomew, conductor and Yale Band, Keith L. Wilson, conductor, Circa 1950
            - Record 1: Medley: Here's to Good Old Yale, Glory for Yale, Boola; Bright College Years; Down the Field; Big Blue Cheering Song (Box 36, Folder 1)
            - Record 2: Bingo; Whoop It Up; Good Night, Poor Harvard; Bulldog; George Washington Bicentennial March (Box 36, Folder 2)
            - Record 3: Eli Yale; Mother of Men; Whiffenpoofs Song (Whiffenpoofs of 1950); Switzer Boy (Box 36, Folder 3)
          - Songs of Yale: Yale Glee Club, Marshall Bartholomew, conductor and Yale Band, Keith L. Wilson, conductor (LP), Circa 1950 (Box 36, Folder 4)
            This long-play record contains all of the songs on the three discs of "Songs of Yale", box 36, folders 1-3.
          - "A Souvenir Album by the Whiffenpoofs, Class of 1942", Circa 1942
            - Record 10: Whiffenpoofs Song; Lucka Lucka Siroka; Shall I, Wasting in Despair?; Mavourneen (Box 36, Folder 5)
            - Record 11: And When the Leaves; We Were Gathering Up the Roses; old Gray Bonnet; Bandolero (Box 36, Folder 6)
            - Record 12: The Moaning Lady; Way Down in My Heart; George Jones: Down Over the Hill (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Bands, general
      - England/France Tour
        - Tour: Beginning to channel crossing, 1994; 1 (Box 37)
        - Yale Band - Air France footage, 1994 June; 1 (Box 38)
        - At the Mermaid Theatre, 1994 June 2; 1 (Box 39)
        - At Cherbourg, France preceded by Yale Precision Marching Band (YPMB) Attack Band, 1994 June 5; 1 (Box 40)
      - Alumni Weekend: random scenes, Yale Concert Band (YCB) & YPMB, 1998 October 23-24; 1 (Box 41)
      - Vox et Musica, for Yale reunions, random, 1999; 1 (Box 42)
      - Sam Evans for Duffy XX celebration, 2002; 1 (Box 43)
      - Nutcracker, 2002; 1 (Box 322)
      - Thomas C. Duffy: 20th Anniversary Tribute, 2002 April 6
        - Copy 1, 1 (Box 44)
        - Copy 2, 1 (Box 45)
      - Band movie, 2004; 1 (Box 323)
      - YBEF Dinner, 2004 October 15; 1 (Box 324)
      - Go Away, 2005 fall; 1 (Box 325)
      - Info CD: Yale Concert Band, Yale Jazz Ensemble, Yale Precision Marching Band, 2006
      - Halloween, 2006; 1 (Box 326)
      - Year in Review, 2008
      - Duffy, 2009; 1 (Box 327)
      - News clips, Heckelphone/Husa, Undated; 1 (Box 46)
      - Generic Highlights, Undated; 1 (Box 47)
      - Miller, Miller, Lawrence, Prior, Undated; 1 (Box 48)
      - Senior segment tape, Undated; 1 (Box 49)
      - Senior segment tape, Undated; 1 (Box 50)
      - Senior segment tape, Undated; 1 (Box 51)
      - Gahm, Undated; 1 (Box 52)
      - The Bandfather edited clips, Undated; 1 (Box 53)
      - Band senior segment Project 'X', Undated; 1 (Box 328)
      - 010 Movie - 1, Undated; 1 (Box 329)
      - 010 Movie - 2, Undated; 1 (Box 330)
      - 010 Movie - 3; 012-Ela-CY, Undated; 1 (Box 331)
      - 012 + Ela + CY, Undated; 1 (Box 332)
      - Halloween, Undated; 1 (Box 333)
      - Band movie 2, Undated; 1 (Box 334)
      - Band Movie 3 - Warren and Mike, Undated; 1 (Box 335)
      - Band Movie 4, Undated; 1 (Box 336)
      - Hamlet Never Dies, project 03, Undated; 1 (Box 337)
      - YIR master for DVD, Undated; 1 (Box 338)
      - Ethan, Undated; 1 (Box 339)
      - Stephanie Chase, Undated; 1 (Box 340)
      - Stephanie's wedding, Undated; 1 (Box 341)
      - Concert for Haiti, Undated
      - Unititled (38B), Undated; 1 (Box 342)
    - Yale Concert Band (YCB)
      - 1812 Overture - Old Campus, 1986; 1 (Box 54)
      - No Strings Attached, 1986 April 18; 1 (Box 55)
      - Twilight Concert (closeups), 1986 May; 1 (Box 56)
      - Liberty Concert (sampler), 1986 October 29; 1 (Box 57)
      - Holiday Concert, 1986 December 5; 1 (Box 58)
      - Oyasato (English), 1987; 1 (Box 552)
      - Adams, 1987 February; 1 (Box 59)
      - Woolsey Hall, 1987 February 13; 1 (Box 60)
      - Japan #1: airplane, Japanese TV, Mt. Fuji, Osaka airport, Tenri, 1987 May; 1 (Box 61)
      - Japan #1/3a, 1987 May; 1 (Box 62)
      - Japan #2/3b, 1987 May; 1 (Box 63)
      - Japan, Tenri, 1987 May; 1 (Box 64)
      - Japan #2: Tenri scenes, scenery en route to Kanazawa, first Kanazawa concert and reception, 1987 May 31; 1 (Box 65)
      - Japan #3: Kanazawa triple header, garden, 1987 June 1-3; 1 (Box 66)
      - Japan #4: Gary Coleman, Matto concert, Komatsu Tech, reception at hotel, changing of the mats, train, 1987 June 1-3; 1 (Box 67)
      - Japan: Kanazawa, 1987 June 1-3; 1 (Box 68)
      - Japan #5: bullet train, Utsunomiya concerts, home stay, 1987 June 3-6; 1 (Box 69)
      - Japan #6: recording sessions, MacDonald's Tokyo, farewell reception, 1987 June 6-7; 1 (Box 70)
      - Japan #7: JBA concert, airports, 1987 June 7; 1 (Box 71)
      - Memoirs of the Orient, 1987 October; 1 (Box 72)
      - 1988 February 12, 1 (Box 73)
      - Save the Church, 1988 April 15; 1 (Box 74)
      - Pineapple Poll, etc., 1988 October 28; 1 (Box 75)
      - 1988 December 2, 1 (Box 76)
      - Italy #1: Plane, museum in Cremona, rain, concert #1 in Salsomaggiore, lightening, drive to/Tower of Pisa, flowers, 1989; 1 (Box 77)
      - Italy #2: Concert in Arezzo, 1989; 1 (Box 78)
      - Italy #3: Concert in Nettuno, 1989; 1 (Box 79)
      - Italy #4: Concert in Villa Borghese, 1989; 1 (Box 80)
      - Italy #5: Concert in Amalfi, 1989; 1 (Box 81)
      - Italy #6: Concert in Salerno, 1989; 1 (Box 82)
      - Inaugural Parade - CBS, Point of View, 1989 January 20; 1 (Box 83)
      - Gershwin - Rhapsody in Blue, 1989 February 10; 1 (Box 84)
      - Italian Concert, 1989 April; 1 (Box 85)
      - 1989 October 27, 1 (Box 86)
      - 1989 December 4, 1 (Box 87)
      - Not in Woolsey, Circa 1990s?; 1 (Box 88)
      - 1990 February 16, 1 (Box 89)
      - CBS news clip, Sousa March, 1990 March; 1 (Box 90)
      - CBDNA Festival Syracuse, 1990 March 3; 1 (Box 91)
      - Fire and Imagination, 1990 April 6; 1 (Box 92)
      - Parents' Night with Yale Jazz Ensemble, Yale Glee Club, Concert Band, Yale Symphony Orchestra, 1990 October 6; 1 (Box 93)
      - Music for Prague 1968, 1990 October 26; 1 (Box 94)
      - Holiday Concert, 1990 November 30; 1 (Box 95)
      - 1991 February 15, 1 (Box 96)
      - Dartmouth, 1991 March 4; 1 (Box 97)
      - Parents' Weekend, 1991 October 5; 1 (Box 98)
      - Demetrius and the Gladiators, 1991 October 25; 1 (Box 99)
      - 1991 December 6, 1 (Box 100)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, New Year's, 1991 December 31; 1 (Box 101)
      - London New Years's Parade, 1992 January 1; 1 (Box 102)
      - 1992 February 14, 1 (Box 103)
      - 1992 April 5, 1 (Box 104)
      - 1992 April 9, 1 (Box 105)
      - 1992 October 23, 1 (Box 106)
      - 1992 December 4, 1 (Box 107)
      - With Malice Toward None, Cronkite (master), 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 108)
      - With Malice Toward None, Cronkite (copy 1), 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 109)
      - With Malice Toward None (copy 2), 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 110)
      - With Malice Toward None, Walter Cronkite, narrator (copy 3), 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 111)
      - With Malice Toward None, Cronkite (copy 4), 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 112)
      - Cronkite, 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 113)
      - Cronkite, Stage Left; Evening, 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 114)
      - Cronkite -- Morning, 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 115)
      - Cronkite - Stage Left, morning, 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 116)
      - Cronkite, 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 117)
      - Thomas C. Duffy, Walter Cronkite, 1993 February 11; 1 (Box 118)
      - 1993 February 11 (Box 540)
      - Rehearsal, 1993 March 28; 1 (Box 119)
      - 1993 April 2, 1 (Box 120)
      - An Exhibition of Musical Pictures, 1993 October 22; 1 (Box 121)
      - With the United States Coast Guard Band, 1993 December 3; 1 (Box 122)
      - "Newsreel" - Hall Memorial High School, 1994 March 21; 1 (Box 123)
      - "Newsreel Yale Remembers WWII"
        - 1994 April 8, 1 (Box 124)
        - Woolsey Hall (copy 1), 1994 April 8; 1 (Box 125)
        - Music director Thomas C. Duffy, Woolsey Hall, 1994 April 8; 1 (Box 126)
        - Second half black and white, 1994 April 8; 1 (Box 127)
        - RAW part 1, 1994 April 8
        - RAW part 2, 1994 April 8
        - Part 2, 1994 April 8
        - Part 2 black and white, 1994 April 8
      - CBS Sunday Morning, Yale Band, 1994 May 29; 1 (Box 128)
      - Yale University Bands England/France Tour
        - At The American College in London, 1994 June 3; 1 (Box 129)
        - At Dinard, France preceded by YPMB Attack Band, 1994 June 6; 1 (Box 130)
        - At The Trianon, 1994 June 9; 1 (Box 131)
        - At Blerancourt, 1994 June 11; 1 (Box 132)
        - Normandy Beaches to end, tape 2 of 2, 1994 June; 1 (Box 133)
      - 1994 October 21, 1 (Box 134)
      - Preludes and Pineapples with Southern Connecticut State University Band, 1994 December; 1 (Box 135)
      - 1994 December 2, 1 (Box 136)
      - Rehearsal, 1995 January 31; 1 (Box 137)
      - With Keith Wilson, Guest Conductor, 1995 February 10; 1 (Box 138)
      - Yale Band, Fox 5 10 O'Clock News, Washington, D.C., 1995 March 31; 1 (Box 139)
      - Glenn Miller sound effects
        - Juke box Saturday night, tape A, 1995; 1 (Box 530)
        - Plane crash and sirens, tape 2, 1995; 1 (Box 531)
        - Plane explosions, tape 3, 1995; 1 (Box 532)
        - Background sounds, plane crash, tape 4, 1995; 1 (Box 533)
        - Dogfights, noise, tape 5, 1995; 1 (Box 534)
        - Engines, tape 6, 1995; 1 (Box 535)
        - Tools, "Sergeant Miller" to music at end, tape 6, 1995; 1 (Box 536)
        - Two machine guns, tape 7, 1995; 1 (Box 537)
        - Engine starting, tape 8, 1995; 1 (Box 538)
        - Guns, battle chaos, tape 9, 1 (Box 539)
      - Glenn Miller, Woolsey, 1995 April 8; 1 (Box 140)
      - A Salute to Victory in Europe, Yale Concert Band, 1995 April 21; 1 (Box 141)
      - Glenn Miller Reunion Concert, Woolsey Hall (with 3 documentary interviews), 1995 May 26; 1 (Box 142)